Ima Joy Chodorow Gandler Texas Jewish collection, Inclusive: 1827-2009, undated, Bulk: 1972-2004
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Genealogy, 1827-2009, undated; 3
  - Schecter, 1979-1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Scheinbrum, 1919-1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Silver, 1979-2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Simmons-Roddy, circa 1884-1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Spark, 1974-1996 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Straus, 1918-2005 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Taub-Trevathan, 1988-1998 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Udashen-Vinokur, 1984-1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Warsaw-Woolf, circa 1903-1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Wessinger, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Wiernir, 1912-1936 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Wizig, circa 1927-2002 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Wohl, 1903-2007 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Wood, 1903-2003 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Wood: Purim Photographs, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Yonack-Zaitchik, 1964-1998 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Organizations, 1873-2009; 4
  The Organizations series is dated 1873-2009. Newsletters, correspondence, research materials, bulletins, and clippings make up the bulk of the items. Other materials include guestbooks, clippings, directories, minutes, announcements, and other printed material. The series is arranged alphabetically by organization and is in good condition.
  - American Jewish Committee, 1934-1988 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - American Jewish Historical Committee, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - American Jewish Historical Society, 1982-2004 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - [Austin] Congregation Beth Israel, 1995-2005 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Austin Jewish Community Center, Book Fair, 1993-2002 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - B’nai B’rith: Anti-defamation League, 1974-1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - B’nai B’rith: General, 1954-2003 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - B’nai B’rith: Hillel Foundation at Texas A&M University, circa 1980-1987 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - B’nai B’rith: Jewish Monthly Magazine, 1982-1998 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - B’nai B’rith: Texarkoma Region Publications, 1998-2005 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - B’nai B’rith: Texas State Association, 1976-1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - B’nai B’rith: [Waco] Eureka Lodge, 1923-1948 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - B’nai B’rith: [Waco] Irving Ginsberg Lodge #198, General, 1948-1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - B’nai B’rith: [Waco] Irving Ginsberg Lodge #198, Newsletters, 1973-1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - B’nai Zion, 2001-2005 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - [Brownsville] Temple Beth El, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - [Bruceville] Greene Family Camp, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - [Bruceville] Greene Family Camp, 1975-1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - [Bruceville] Greene Family Camp, 1982 -1983 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - [Bruceville] Greene Family Camp, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - [Bruceville] Greene Family Camp, 1986-1989 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - [Bruceville] Greene Family Camp, 1989 -1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - [Bruceville] Greene Family Camp, 1991-1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - [Bruceville] Greene Family Camp, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - [Bruceville] Greene Family Camp, 2000-2009 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - [College Station] Texas A&M Hillel, 1989-2008 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - [Corpus Christi] Temple Beth El, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - [Corsicana] Agudas Achim and Temple Beth El, 1982-1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Council of Jewish Federations, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - [Dallas] Brookhaven Country Club, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - [Dallas] Congregation Shearith Israel, 2000-2005 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Dallas: General, 1982-1998 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - [Dallas] Golden Acres, 1996-2000 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Dallas Jewish Coalition for the Homeless, 1994-2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Dallas Jewish Historical Society, 1994-2009 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - [Dallas] Temple Emanu-El: Correspondence, 1995-2004 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - [Dallas] Temple Emanu-El: Financial, 1999-2002 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - [Dallas] Temple Emanu-El: Newsletters, 1994-1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - [Dallas] Temple Emanu-El: Newsletters, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - [Dallas] Temple Emanu-El: Newsletters, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - [Dallas] Temple Emanu-El: Newsletters, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - [Dallas] Temple Emanu-El: Newsletters, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - [Dallas] Temple Emanu-El: Newsletters, 2002-2004 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - [Dallas] Temple Emanu-El: Sisterhood, 1994-2004 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - [Dallas] Temple Emanu-El: Programming, 1994-2004 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - [Dallas] Temple Emanu-El: Services, 1995-2006 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Greater Waco Interfaith Conference (Waco Conference of Christians and Jews), 1980-1999 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Greater Waco Interfaith Conference (Waco Conference of Christians and Jews), 2000-2004 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Greater Waco Interfaith Conference (Waco Conference of Christians and Jews), 2005 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Greater Waco Interfaith Conference (Waco Conference of Christians and Jews), 2006-2007 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Greater Waco Interfaith Conference (Waco Conference of Christians and Jews), 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Goldring/Woldenberg Institute of Southern Jewish Life: General, 1998-2002 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Goldring/Woldenberg Institute of Southern Jewish Life: Newsletters, 1995-2002 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Goldring/Woldenberg Institute of Southern Jewish Life: Newsletters, 2003-2008 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Hadassah, 1979-2009 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Hebrew Rest Association, 1873-1998 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Hebrew Rest Cemetery, 1994-2002 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Hebrew Rest Cemetery, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Hebrew Union College: Jewish Institute of Religion, 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - [Houston] Congregation Beth Israel: Newsletters, 1986-1999 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - [Houston] Congregation Beth Israel: Services, 1985-2008 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - [Houston] Congregation Emanu-El, 1984-2009 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - International Association of Hebrew Free Loans, 1998-2001 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - [Jefferson] Hebrew Cemetery Association, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Children’s Regional Service, 1981-2004 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Community Center of Dallas, 1986-2004 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Community Council of Greater Waco, 2006-2008 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Community School of Central Texas, 1992-2002 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Family Services, circa 1998-2009 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Federated Charities, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Federation of Greater Dallas, 1984-2009 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas (Jewish Welfare Council of Waco and Central Texas), circa 1945-1959 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas (Jewish Welfare Council of Waco and Central Texas), 1960-1970 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas (Jewish Welfare Council of Waco and Central Texas), 1972-1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas (Jewish Welfare Council of Waco and Central Texas), 1980-1996 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas, 1988 -1989 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas, 1990-2000 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas, 2000-2006 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas: Jacob de Cordova Historic Landmark Guests and Guestbook, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas: Jacob de Cordova Historic Landmark Proclamation, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas: Jacob de Cordova Historic Landmark Research, 1936-1986 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Federation of Waco and Central Texas: Jacob de Cordova Historic Landmark Research, 1910-1986 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Historical Society of Memphis and the Mid-South, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Ladies Hebrew Aid Society, 1879-1884 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - [Laredo] Temple B’nai Israel, 1924-2002 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - [Longview] Temple Emanu-El, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - [McAllen] Temple Emanuel, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - National Conference of Jewish Women: Texas State Conference, Houston, Texas, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - National Council of Jewish Women, 1962-2008 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - National Council of Jewish Women, Minette Wood, 1926-1938 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section: Correspondence, 1974-2005 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section, Correspondence, 1996-2009 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section, Newsletters, Bulletin, 1987-1999 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section, Newsletters, Bulletin, 2001-2009 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section, Programing, 1987-2008 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section, Yearbook, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section, Yearbook, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section, Yearbook (1 of 2), 1994- 1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section, Yearbook (2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section, Yearbook, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section, Yearbook, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section, Yearbook, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section Evening Branch, General, 1987-2004 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section Evening Branch, Newsletters, Constant Comment, 1987-2004 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Greater Dallas Section Evening Branch, Newsletters, Constant Comment, 1995-2004 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Waco Section, 1922-1998 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Waco Section, 1931-1953 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - [National] Federation of Temple Sisterhoods: 20th Biennial Assembly, 1955-1964 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - [National] Federation of Temple Sisterhoods: 30th Biennial Assembly (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - [National] Federation of Temple Sisterhoods: 30th Biennial Assembly (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - [National] Federation of Temple Sisterhoods: General, 1963-1985 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - [National] Federation of Temple Sisterhoods: Texas-Oklahoma Federation #22, circa 1960-1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - [National] Federation of Temple Sisterhoods: Women of Reform Judaism General, 2000-2002 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - [National] Federation of Temple Sisterhoods: Women Reform Judaism, Texas Oklahoma Federation #22, 1998-2004 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - North American Conference of Ethiopian Jewry, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - National Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - [San Antonio] Congregation Agudas Achim, 1961-2006 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - [San Antonio] Temple Beth-El, 1964-2004 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Southern Jewish Historical Society: 24th Annual Conference, Richmond, Virginia, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Southern Jewish Historical Society: Conferences, 1979-2008 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Southern Jewish Historical Society: General, 1979-2005 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Southern Jewish Historical Society: Membership, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Southern Jewish Historical Society: Newsletters, 1980-1987 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Southern Jewish Historical Society: Newsletters, 1995-2006 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Southern Jewish Historical Society: Southern Jewish History Volume 7, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Southern Jewish Historical Society: Southern Jewish History Volume 8, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Texas: General, 1987-2005 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society, 1979-1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society, 1985-1987 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society, 1986-1991 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society, 1996-1999 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society, 2000-2004 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society, 2003-2008 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society: Annual Meeting, Hot Springs Arkansas, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society: Newsletters, 1982-2003 (Box 1 OVZ, Item 7)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society: Newsletters, 1982-1989 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society: Newsletters, 1990-1994 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society: Newsletters, 1994-1998 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Texas Jewish Historical Society: Newsletters, 2001-2002 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Texas Young Judea, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: 53rd General Assembly, Dallas, Texas, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: 57th General Assembly, Houston, Texas, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: 59th General Assembly, Chicago, Illinois (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: 59th General Assembly, Chicago, Illinois (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: 64th General Assembly, Dallas, Texas, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: Constitution and By-laws, 1973-1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: Directories, 1976-1982 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: General, 1975-1998 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: General Assembly, 1979-1989 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: Proposals and Resolutions, 1975-1983 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: Publications, 1996-2001 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: Reports and Publications, 1975-1994 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: Southwest Council, General, 1975-1990 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: Southwest Council, Biennial Convention, 1990-2002 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: Southwest Council Biennial Convention, Corpus Christi, Texas, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Union of American Jewish Congregations: Southwest Council Biennial Convention, Shreveport, Louisiana, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - United Jewish Appeal, 1938-1996 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - United States Holocaust Memorial Museum, 1993-2003 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - United Synagogue of America, 1984-2001 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - [Waco] Chavurah, 1984-1995 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Waco Committee for State of Israel Bonds, 1969-1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Aliyah Dinner, 1982-1999 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Anniversary Programs, 1884-1973 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Board of Trustees, 1947-2004 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Building Fund, circa 1922-1973 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Bulletins, 1946-2009 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Bulletins, 1947-2006 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Cemetery, 1948-1984 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Clippings, 1933-2008 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Constitution and By-laws, 1888 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Correspondence, 1954-1998 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Financial, 1904-1984 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: High Holy Day Preparation, 1972-1996 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: History, 1888-2000 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Homecoming Weekend, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Jewish Burial Records, Waco, 1982-1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Junior Benefit Club, 1934 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Membership, 1936-1998 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Membership Ledger, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Monument Unveilings, 1980-2005 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Mourning Practices, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Photographs, 1893-1985 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Programing, 1954-2008 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Rabbis, 1967-1999 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Services, Confirmation and Bar Mitzvahs, 1929-1996 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Services, Holiday and Special, 1954-2008 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Services, General, 1954-1998 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Sisterhood, 1954-1979 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Sisterhood, 1980-1995 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Sisterhood, Directories and Yearbook, 1965-1995 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Synagogue Dedication, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - [Waco] Congregation Agudath Jacob: Yahrzeit Reminders, 1978-1994 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Waco Federation of Temple Youth, circa 1968-1994 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Waco Jewish Federation Texas Sesquicentennial Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Waco Jewish Federation Texas Sesquicentennial Committee, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Waco Jewish Federation Texas Sesquicentennial Committee: Jacob de Cordova Historical Marker Unveiling, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Waco Jewish Federation Texas Sesquicentennial Committee: Multimedia Presentation (1 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Waco Jewish Federation Texas Sesquicentennial Committee: Multimedia Presentation (2 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Waco Jewish Federation Texas Sesquicentennial Committee: Multimedia Presentation (3 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - [Waco] Ridgewood Country Club: Rambler, 1998-2004 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - [Waco] Ridgewood Country Club: Rambler, 2006-2007 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: 125th Anniversary, 2003-2008 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: 125th Anniversary Committee, 1910-1927 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: 125th Anniversary, Committee Notes, 1879-1988 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Building Construction and Dedication, 1880-1910 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Bulletins, 1919-1972 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Bulletins, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Constitution and By-laws, 1962-2007 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Correspondence, 100th Anniversary and Confirmation Class Project, 1972-1979 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Correspondence, 100th Anniversary and Confirmation Class Project, 1917-1980 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Correspondence, General, circa 1957-2007 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Financial Documents, 1935-1939 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Financial Records, 1881-1960 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: History, 1984-2005 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: History and General Notes, 1984-circa 2003 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Membership, 1909 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Membership, 1961-2008 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Minutes, 1961-2005 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Photographs, Annual Picnic at Greene Family Camp, 1975-1979 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Photographs, Congregational Dinners and Meetings, 1975-1979 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Photographs, Congregational Dinners and Meetings, 1981-1984 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Photographs, General, 1893-1950 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Photographs, General, 1961-1990 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Photographs, Religious School Model Seder, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Photographs, Sisterhood Luncheon Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Photographs, Sukkot and Chanukah, 1983-1986 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Photographs, Waco Federation of Temple Youth, 1979-1985 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Programing and Services, 1928-2008 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Religious School, circa 1950-1986 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Sisterhood, circa 1918-1976 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Sisterhood, 1965-1969 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Sisterhood, 1970-1980 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Sisterhood, 1982-2009 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Sisterhood, Yearly Report, 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Speeches and Eulogies, 1979-2008 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Temple Dedication, circa 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Temple Dedication, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Texas State Historical Marker, 1961-2007 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Yom Kippur Memorial, 2005-2007 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - [Waco] Temple Rodef Sholom: Yom Kippur Memorial Lists, 1992-2001 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Waco Zionist District, 1928 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - World Jewish Congress, 1988-2004 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- General, 1924-1996; 5
  The General series is dated 1924-1996. Title abstracts, property records, correspondence, clippings, research notes, committee engagement notes, organizational directories, and handbooks are present. The series is in alphabetical order and in good condition.
  - Abstract of Title: Belle Meade Court Addition, City of Waco, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Abstract of Title: Lot 10, Block 10, Central Villa Addition, City of Waco, 1945-1961 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Abstract of Title: Part Lots 8 and 9, Block 13, Glenwood Addition, City of Waco, 1928-1936 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Abstract of Title: Part Lots 8 and 9, Block 13, Glenwood Addition, City of Waco, 1928 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Abstract of Title: Part Lots 8 and 9, Block 13, Glenwood Addition, City of Waco, 1952-1966 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Abstract of Title: Lots 2,3,4,8,9,10, 11, and 12, Block 1, J.F. Davis Addition, City of Waco, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Abstract of Title: Lot 6, Block 48, Provident Addition, City of Waco, 1945-1967 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Abstract of Title: Lots 2 and 3, Block 17, Renick Addition, City of Waco, 1924-1934 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Abstract of Title: Lots 9 and 10, Block 10, Renick Addition, City of Waco, 1948-1950 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Abstract of Title: Lot 2, Block 9, Turner, Clinton, and Turner Addition, City of Waco, 1930-1945 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Abstract of Title: Lots 1,2,3, Block 3, Turner, Clinton, and Turner Addition, City of Waco, 1924-1953 (Box 43, Folder 6)